bargello.com 2017-12-02

# Bargello.com Privacy Policy, Cookies, Information

**Bargello.com Privacy Policy**

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists managed and/or owned and/or operated by Bargello.com 

The following discloses our Privacy Policy. 

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computerâ€™s "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the web sites owned and/or managed by Bargello.com, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitorâ€™s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computerâ€™s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of our web sites you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. We may also use cookies to ascertain how many times youâ€™ve seen an advertisement. Our advertisers/clients and/or we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our Site/s. 

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

**What other information do you request?**

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about seminars, etc.). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. 

When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

**What information do you collect when I purchase something?**

When you are purchasing something from our website, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address and any other details necessary to process and fulfil your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used to notify you of related product and services but it will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your consent . Your credit card number, expiration date and payments taken will always be recorded using a secure server with 2Checkout.com.

Some of the sites that we own or manage use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. 

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

We will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  * Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on the web sites managed or owned by Bargello.com. 
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of the web sites managed or owned by Bargello.com or its/their visitors. 
  * Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties. 
  * Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities. 

Bargello.com uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Bargello.com reserves the right to transfer information in connection with the sale of all or part of web sites managed and/or owned by Bargello.comâ€™s capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. Web sites managed and/or owned by Bargello.com also link to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever youâ€™re online. 

**Your Consent To This Agreement**

By using the Web sites managed and/or owned by Bargello.com, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
